https://www.eyedentity.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - EYEdentity Products
Skip to navigation Skip to content
Search for:
Search
MenuHomeShopMammal EyesDoll and Figurine EyesBird EyesFish EyesReptile and Amphibian EyesBlack and Uncoloured EyesCustom EyesInformationProduct TypesPostage and Delivery InformationTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyContact UsLoginHomeCheckoutContact UsCookie SettingsMy AccountPrivacy PolicyShopCustom EyesPostage and Delivery InformationProduct TypesAspheric Glass EyesEurope Eyes (Acrylic)Flat Glass EyesFlex Eyes (Plastic)Glass Eyes in CC-ShapeGlass Eyes in IQ-ShapeGlass Eyes on WireGlass LensesMouth Blown EyesSolid Glass EyesSpecial ShapesTohickon Glass EyesShopping BasketSpecial OrdersTerms and Conditions
£0.00 0 items Home / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how EYEdentity Products uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. EYEdentity Products takes privacy and security seriously. We do not sell or share names, email addresses, or any other personal information with third parties. EYEdentity Products is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.EYEdentity Products may change this policy occasionally by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy was most recently updated on May 25, 2018 to reflect changes put into place by Europe’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).Table of contentsWho we areWhat information do we collectWhat do we use your information forHow do we protect your informationHow do we use cookiesAnalyticsUpdate your privacy settingsDo we disclose any information to third partiesHow long we retain your dataWhat rights you have over your dataRequest to export or erase your dataWhere we send your dataOur contact informationOur data breach proceduresWhat third parties we receive data fromWhat automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataWho we areEYEdentity Products are glass and acrylic eye suppliers to both trade and public based in the United Kingdom. You can find out more about us in our About Us and Contact Us pages.Our website address is: https://www.eyedentity.co.ukWhat information do we collect?For all customers, (i.e. people who have created an account with https://www.eyedentity.co.uk we collect the following personal details:name (required)address (required)contact email address (required)country (required)phone number (required)payment details such as credit card information are collected via SAGE or PayPal and not stored on our servers only the payment email address, customer name and address are stored on our server and all data is transferred via (SSL) Secure Sockets Layer, the most widely used security protocol for over internet communications.For all visitors to our website and subscribers, we collect:Anonymised and non-personal information via Google Analytics, such as country, browser type and device, (this helps us better understand how subscribers use our site, so we can make improvements and offer a better experience).Anonymised technical details of your device, used to enforce our paywall (Paywall refers to restricted access to content or listings via free or paid packages)For all newsletter subscribers (i.e. people who have subscribed to receive one or more of our newsletters), we collect the following personal details:email address (required)name and country (optional)What do we use your information for?We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keepingTo improve our website, products and servicesTo process transactionsEnforce our paywallProvide support when requested, for instance with a subscription, purchase or login issueHow do we protect your information?We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. These security measures include, but are not limited to: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information and SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the internet securely.How do we use cookies?A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site as well as helping to speed up load times.For instance, when you sign in and select “Remember me”, this choice can only be applied with the use of a cookie.Likewise, if you have an account and you log in to our website, we will set up cookies to save your login information, these cookies last for one session. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for 30 days. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.We only use cookies for essential website functionalities as per the examples above, and for analytics purposes – for instance, to distinguish between a new, and returning, visitors.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by remembering your choices, and providing us with more accurate analytics.A cookie in no way gives us any access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.To view and/or update your cookies preferences, please visit our Cookie Settings. Controlling the use of cookiesYou may at any point disable cookies by choosing this in your browser. These settings are usually found in the “internet options” or “tools” menus in the browser.We would like to point out that there are tools that can monitor and give you overview about which cookies are placed by the web services you visit. To read more about cookies and how you delete them, see for instance www.allaboutcookies.org .Please note that some of our functionality and Services will not function if you disable cookies. Your browser will for example not remember your credentials automatically.AnalyticsWe use the following analytics services on our website:Google Analytics. This allows us to monitor overall traffic and segment it by for instance page title, country, screen resolution or browser. Doing so allows us to track our content popularity, gauge where our audience is located across the world and what screen resolutions are the most common in our readership, for instance. It also allows us to carry out AB tests to inform our paywall. The data collected by Google Analytics is fully anonymised and you may opt out of the cookie it adds on our Cookie Settings pageUpdate your privacy settingsYou may update all your privacy preferences at any time, on our Cookie Settings page.Do we disclose any information to third parties?EYEdentity Products https://www.eyedentity.co.uk does not share your data with any third party. We adhere to a strict policy of never selling, distributing or leasing your personal information to third parties, unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us at sales@eyedentity.co.ukIf you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.How long do we retain your dataHow long we retain certain data depends on what we are using it for, whether that is to provide beneficial services to you, legitimate interests (described above) for our company EYEdentity Products and https://www.eyedentity.co.uk or so that we can comply with the law. If you cease to be a customer or user, we will archive your data no later than 8 weeks after you stop using the website.For visitors who register on our website, we store all account information indefinitely, for record keeping purposes. All subscribers can see, edit, or delete their personal information (with the exception of the username) at any time in their account page. Website administrators can also see and edit the information, except for the password which can only be reset by the user in the account section or requested via email reset link.For anyone who has made a purchase through our website, we will retain a record of the transaction history, invoice(s) and billing details indefinitely for accounting and tax auditing purposes. This history is also visible in subscribers’ Account Page, in the Billing Details and Your Listings page.What rights you have over your dataIndividuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their personal data.Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us.If you have an account on this site, have made a transaction on our website, or subscribe to our newsletters, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. We do not hold personal data on any other visitors.You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you by contacting us. Please note this does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, billing, legal, or security purposes.Request to export or erase your dataIf you would like us to export, or erase, all the data we may hold about you, please click below and request that we delete it or export it to you.EXPORT OR DELETE MY DATAWhere we send your dataAs an online business, we use third party hosting and cloud technologies to support our operations. This means our traffic may be routed to, or some of our data processed or stored with, the services listed below in this section.When we share data with these providers, it may be transferred to, and processed in, countries other than the United Kingdom – such as to the United States, where most of the services we use are headquartered.For individuals in the European Economic Area (EEA), this means that your data may be transferred outside of the EEA. Where your personal data is transferred outside the EEA, it will only be transferred to countries that have been identified as providing adequate protection for EEA data, or that can show certified compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield and Swiss-US Privacy Shield framework (collectively, the “Privacy Shields”).All information is sent and stored using password protected directories and databases and Secure Sockets Layered (SSL) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the internet securely.The third parties https://www.eyedentity.co.uk relies on are:DreamHost web hosting are based in the United States and are GDPR compliant. Learn more about DreamHosts Data Processing  and compliance with the EU’s General Directive on Privacy Regulation (GDPR) here. Comodo Cyber Security, are based in the US, they provide our SSL Certificate, (Secure Sockets Layer) it is the most widely deployed cryptographic protocol to provide security over internet communications SSL Certificates are small data files that digitally bind a cryptographic key to an organisations details. When installed on a web server, it activates the padlock and the https protocol and allows secure connections from a web server to a browser. Typically, SSL is used to secure credit card transactions, data transfer and logins, and more recently is becoming the norm when securing browsing of social media sites. Comodo Cyber Security(s) privacy policy can be found here.MailChimp, the campaign automation platform owned by US-based Rocket Science Group. MailChimp stores our newsletter subscribers’ data in order to send newsletters on our behalf. MailChimp is also a certified member of the Privacy Shields. Learn more about its privacy policy here.PayPal, a US-based payment gateway provider which allows us to securely process payments on your behalf for our services. PayPal is also a certified member of the Privacy Shields. Learn more about its privacy policy hereStripe, a US-based payment gateway provider which allows us to securely process payments on your behalf for our services. Stripe is also a certified member of the Privacy Shields. Learn more about its privacy policy here.Payments made via SAGEPAY gateway are subject to terms and conditions set out here https://www.sagepay.co.uk/policiesGoogle Analytics, owned by Google and uses wholly anonymised analytics. Google is a US-based company and member of the Privacy Shields. Read their privacy policy hereOur Contact InformationFor matters specific to privacy matters, please contact us at sales@eyedentity.co.ukWhat third parties we receive data fromWe occasionally receive access to lists of attendees from specific industry events. In this case, we will always first ask proof from the provider that the attendees have provided consent for their details to be shared with third parties before receiving the list.What automated decision making and / or profiling we do with user dataSome of the contextual data provided by our subscribers – specifically industry, country and job title – is used to collate statistics on our audience, where these details are available. This helps us make better business and editorial decisions by having a better understanding of who our audience is. Note: we would never use any personably identifiable information for such processes.Product CategoriesSelect a categoryBird Eyes  (274)   Art. 115  (27)   Art. 120  (15)   Art. 125  (16)   Art. 180  (26)   Art. 180AF  (21)   Art. 180AFT  (5)   Art. 180EE  (18)   Art. 180FB  (4)   Art. 185  (46)   Art. 185 EE  (46)   Art. 185AF  (21)   Art. 185AFBL  (5)   Art. 185AFFL  (8)   Art. 185FB  (8)   Art. 500  (8)Black and Uncoloured Eyes  (46)   Art. 100  (1)   Art. 101  (1)   Art. 103  (1)   Art. 105  (1)   Art. 110  (1)   Art. 110T  (1)   Art. 135  (1)   Art. 135S  (1)   Art. 140  (1)   Art. 140 AFK  (1)   Art. 140AF  (1)   Art. 140AFKS  (1)   Art. 140AFPP  (1)   Art. 140AFS  (1)   Art. 140FB  (1)   Art. 140FBS  (1)   Art. 140G  (1)   Art. 140GS  (1)   Art. 140K  (1)   Art. 140KS  (1)   Art. 140S  (1)   Art. 145  (1)   Art. 145OP  (1)   Art. 145S  (1)   Art. 150  (1)   Art. 150B  (1)   Art. 150K  (1)   Art. 150KS  (1)   Art. 150LU  (1)   Art. 150LUS  (1)   Art. 150S  (1)   Art. 155  (1)   Art. 155AF  (1)   Art. 155AFS  (1)   Art. 155HK  (1)   Art. 155HKS  (1)   Art. 155NF  (1)   Art. 155NFS  (1)   Art. 155S  (1)   Art. 210  (1)   Art. 210FB  (1)   Art. 210H  (1)   Art. 450MX  (1)   Art. 540  (1)   Art. 540S  (1)   Art. 750MSX  (1)Custom Orders  (0)Doll and Figurine Eyes  (178)   Ar. 700MPW  (7)   Art. 400P  (8)   Art. 403P  (6)   Art. 445PO  (5)   Art. 450M  (6)   Art. 450MA  (6)   Art. 450MR  (6)   Art. 450MRA  (6)   Art. 700  (47)   Art. 700A  (47)   Art. 700MP  (6)   Art. 750MS  (6)   Art. 750MSA  (6)   Art. 800  (6)   Art. 800MK  (5)   Art. 800MKA  (5)Fish Eyes  (88)   Art. 160  (15)   Art. 160AF  (17)   Art. 160FE  (8)   Art. 160HK  (10)   Art. 160NF  (9)   Art. 200  (17)   Art. 200FB  (7)   Art. 200H  (5)Human Eyes  (26)   Art. 900HF  (4)   Art. 900HFA  (4)   Art. 900P  (9)   Art. 900PA  (9)Mammal Eyes  (181)   Art. 190 OV  (27)   Art. 190AF  (5)   Art. 190BO  (8)   Art. 190BR  (7)   Art. 190BS  (3)   Art. 190C  (13)   Art. 190EE  (7)   Art. 190IP  (3)   Art. 190IPRC  (1)   Art. 190IPT  (5)   Art. 190IQ  (4)   Art. 190MB  (3)   Art. 190MBXF  (3)   Art. 190MBXH  (3)   Art. 190MBXM  (3)   Art. 190MBXR  (2)   Art. 190OVSP  (2)   Art. 190RD  (29)   Art. 190TO  (10)   Art. 195  (29)   Art. 195LU  (6)   Art. 199FH  (1)   Art. 250IQR  (7)Reptile and Amphibian Eyes  (47)   Art. 130AF  (2)   Art. 130CC  (7)   Art. 130DR  (5)   Art. 132  (19)   Art. 132A  (12)   Art. 132RS  (2)Teddy Bear Eyes  (18)   Art. 100 OE  (1)   Art. 100MOE  (1)   Art. 110 OE  (1)   Art. 110 TOE  (8)   Art. 125OE  (7)Uncategorized  (0) Copyright © 2020 EYEdentity ProductsThe Manor House · Church Hill · Saxmundham IP17 1EU · United Kingdom01728 603171sales@eyedentity.co.uk © EYEdentity Products 2020
Privacy PolicyBuilt with Storefront & WooCommerce. My Account Search Search for:
Search
0
This Site Uses Cookies: To make www.eyedentity.co.uk work properly and offer you the best user experience, we use cookies. If you’re ok with that, just continue, if you want to find out more you can click on our read more button below. AcceptRead more
